A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1968-1969
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Files, 1968-1969
  - National Defense Education Act (National Defense Student Loan) 1968-1969 (Box 57)
  - National Historical Publications Commission (see also Adams, Madison Papers) 1968-1969 (Box 57)
  - Institutional Support Programs for the Fiscal Year 1968 1968-1969 (Box 57)
  - National Science Foundation 1968-1969 (Box 57)
  - National Science Advisory Commission for Institutional Relations 1968-1969 (Box 57)
  - National Science Foundation Institutional Grant for science 1968-1969 (Box 57)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - National War College 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - National War College (folder containing 5 books) 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - Navy - General 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - Navy - ROTC 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - Navy League of the United States 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - Navy League of the United States (blue folder) 1968-1969 (Box 58)
  - Newcomb Hall (see also Committee - University Union) 1968-1969 (Box 59)
  - Newcomen Speech 1968-1969 (Box 59)
  - Newcomen Society 1968-1969 (Box 59)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1968-1969 (Box 60)
  - Newsletter 1968-1969 (Box 60)
  - Nursing (see Medical Center) 1968-1969 (Box 60)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 60)
  - Office Invoices 1968-1969 (Box 60)
  - Office Invoices 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - Office Travel 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - Office of Institutional Research 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 61)
  - "Pi - Pz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 62)
  - Personnel - Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 62)
  - Personnel Relative Applications, "A - Z" 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Personnel Profiles 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Personnel - Fringe Benefit Sheets 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Personnel (State employees - Richmond and Local Offices) 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Personnel - Memo on Personnel Procedure 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Council 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Philosophy 1968-1969 (Box 63)
  - Physics 1968-1969 (Box 64)
  - Physics Department 1968-1969 (Box 64)
  - Planning Department (see also Individual Building Programs) 1968-1969 (Box 64)
  - Planning Division (State) 1968-1969 (Box 64)
  - Project Status Reports 1968-1969 (Box 64)
  - Provost of the University (includes Assistant Provost and Associate Provost for Res.) 1968-1969 (Box 65)
  - Radio 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Raven Society 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Recommendations, "A - Z" 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Registrar - General 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Registrar - Student Reports 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Rehabilitation Center 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Religious Studies 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - Romance Languages 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - "S - Sl" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 66)
  - "Sm - Ss" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 67)
  - "St - Sz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 67)
  - Salaries (see also Personnel) 1968-1969 (Box 67)
  - Security, Department of 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Selective Service 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Senate, University 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Seven Society 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Sociology and Anthropology 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools - FINAL REPORT, COMMITTEE TO VISIT THE UNIV. OF VA., NOVEMBER 1964 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund (see also Council of Southern Universities) 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Southern Regional Education Board: 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - 1) STATE and LOCAL REVENUE POTENTIAL (2 books) (Box 68)
  - 2) THE COLLEGE CAMPUS IN 1969 (Box 68)
  - 3) THE ORGANIZATION OF HIGHER EDUCATION - PROCEEDINGS (Box 68)
  - 4) ANNUAL MEETING, JUNE 1968 (Box 68)
  - 5) SOUTHERN REGIONAL EDUCATION BOARD (Box 68)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1968-1969 (Box 69)
  - Southern University Conference 1968-1969 (Box 69)
  - Speeches 1968-1969 (Box 69)
  - Speech and Drama 1968-1969 (Box 70)
  - Sponsored Programs 1968-1969 (Box 70)
  - State Board of Education 1968-1969 (Box 70)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1968-1969 (Box 70)
  - Student Affairs 1968-1969 (Box 71)
  - Student Aid Foundation (see Virginia Student Aid Foundation- VSAF) 1968-1969 (Box 71)
  - Student Council 1968-1969 (Box 72)
  - Student Council - Fall 1968: Minutes 1968-1969 (Box 72)
  - Student Counseling Center 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Student Health Department 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Student Legal Forum 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Student Placement 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Summer Session Finals 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Traffic Control 1968-1969 (Box 74)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 74)
  - United Givers Fund 1968-1969 (Box 74)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization 1968-1969 (Box 75)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture 1968-1969 (Box 76)
  - U. S. Department of Defense 1968-1969 (Box 76)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare 1968-1969 (Box 76)
  - U.S. Public Health Service 1968-1969 (Box 76)
  - U. S. Department of State 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Center in Virginia 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Hall (see also Committee - Field House) 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Houses - General 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Houses - Faulkner House 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Houses - "Morea" 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Printing Office 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - University Relations 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - Universities Research Association 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - Upward Bound 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Legislative Advisory Council (see Legislative Program and Budget Files) 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Education Association 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Historical Society (see also Madison Papers) 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science - FACT-FOLDER 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation (VSAF) 1968-1969 (Box 78)
  - Visitors - General 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - General 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Educational Policy 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Executive 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Finance 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Buildings and Grounds 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Mary Washington College 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Medical 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Board Committees - Student Affairs and Athletics 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Docket - 4 October 1968 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Minutes - 4 October 1968 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Docket - 14 December 1968 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Minutes - 14 December 1968 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Docket - 15 February 1969 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Minutes - 15 February 1969 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Docket - 5 April 1969 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Minutes - 5 April 1969 1968-1969 (Box 80)
  - Visitors - Docket - 6 June 1969 1968-1969 (Box 81)
  - Visitors - Minutes - 6 June 1969 1968-1969 (Box 81)
  - "W - Wh" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 81)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 81)
  - Water Resources 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - Wheeler-Bennett, Sir John (Scholar in Residence) 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - Walpole Society 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - Women, Dean of 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - THE WORLD EDUCATIONAL CRISIS, A SYSTEMS ANALYSIS by Philip H. Coombs 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box 82)
  - YMCA 1968-1969 (Box 82)